ACTWU's Secretary-Treasurer's Office Records 5619/018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Union Management Summit Meeting, 1997 (Box 135, Folder 5)
- UNITE General Fund, 1995 (Box 135, Folder 6)
- ILGWU General Fund, 1995 (Box 135, Folder 7)
- ILGWU General Fund '94, 1994 (Box 135, Folder 8)
- Xerox, 1996 (Box 135, Folder 9)
- UNITE auto parts plants: Industrial Audit Survey, 1996 (Box 135, Folder 10)
- ACI (automated concepts incorporated), 1996 (Box 135, Folder 11)
- Brandywine asset Management Inc., 1996 (Box 135, Folder 12)
- Levi's Task Force, 1993 (Box 135, Folder 13)
- Sale of Bank Stock -- ABNY, 1994 (Box 135, Folder 14)
- ABNY -- Audit Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 135, Folder 15)
- GEB March 1986 research Reports, 1991-1995 (Box 135, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Bank of New York - ABNY, 1993 (Box 135, Folder 17)
- ABNY -- Executive Committee G. Caprio, 1993-1995 (Box 135, Folder 18)
- ABNY Exec. Committee Minutes, 1992 (Box 135, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Washable Clothing, Sportswear, and Allied Industries Fund, 1991 (Box 135, Folder 20)
- Benefit Plans, 1988-1989 (Box 135, Folder 21)
- ASRP--TSRP, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 2)
- "Window" Program 1991 (Box 136, Folder 3)
- ASRP-General, 1990-1991 (Box 136, Folder 4)
- Amendments to the Amalgamated Staff retirement Plan - 1989 (Box 136, Folder 5)
- Annual Return - Amalgamates Staff Retirement Plan, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Bank of New York Offering of Class B Common Stock, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Bank, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Bank Shareholders, 1989 (Box 136, Folder 9)
- ABNY Board of Directors Meetings., 1991 (Box 136, Folder 10)
- Ensign Bank Resolution, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 11)
- Nicholas Palermo Correspondence, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Bank of New York Misc., 1990 (Box 136, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Bank of New York Misc. #2, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Service & Allied Industries Insurance Fund, 1990-1991 (Box 136, Folder 15)
- Business Plan for Amalgamated Services Corporation booklet #1, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 16)
- Business Plan for Amalgamated Services Corporation booklet #2, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 17)
- Duff and Phelps Financial Consulting co., 1991 (Box 136, Folder 18)
- Arthur Loevy, ACTWU letters, 1990-1991 (Box 136, Folder 19)
- ACTWU/Levi's Labor-Management Relations Task Force, 1994 (Box 136, Folder 20)
- 1994 Actuarial Valuation Report (Box 136, Folder 21)
- Audited Financial Statements and Schedule (ACTWU), 1992 (Box 136, Folder 22)
- Sandler O'Neill, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 23)
- Amalgamated Neckwear Workers Insurance & Retirement Funds, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 24)
- Employee Retirement Plan of ABNY, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 25)
- ABNY Pension Expense and Disclosure Information, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 26)
- Actuarial Valuation for the Textile Staff Retirement Plan U.S. Participant, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 1)
- Actuarial Valuation of the Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 2)
- Pension Plans, October 1, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 3)
- Actuarial Valuation for the Textile Staff Retirement Plan U.S. Participants, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 4)
- Actuarial Valuation of the Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment Retirement Fund, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries Retirement Fund, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment Retirement Fund, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 8)
- Actuarial Valuation for the Textile Staff Retirement Plan U.S. Participants, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 9)
- Annual Return/Report of Employee Benefit plan, 1989 (Box 137, Folder 10)
- Actuarial Valuation of the Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 11)
- Actuarial Valuation of the Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 12)
- The Amalgamated Washable Clothing, Sportswear and Allied Industries Fund Retirement Fund, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 13)
- Actuarial Valuation for the Textile Staff Retirement Plan U.S. Participants, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 14)
- The Amalgamated Washable Clothing, Sportswear and Allied Industries Fund Retirement Plan, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 15)
- The Amalgamated Washable Clothing. Sportswear and Allied Industries Fund Retirement Plan, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment Retirement Fund, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 17)
- Actuarial Valuation of the Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 18)
- MDSASS, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Life ASC Valuation Analysis, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Funds '93, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 21)
- Employee Benefit Plans '91-'92, 1991-1992 (Box 137, Folder 22)
- Employee Benefit Plans '89-'92, 1989-1992 (Box 137, Folder 23)